https://www.attorneygeneral.gov/accessibility-policy/

Do Not Call List
Do you receive unwanted calls? Check or add your phone numbers to the Pennsylvania Do Not Call Registry.
Concealed Carry Agreements
Voters’ Rights in Effect at the Polling Places on Election Days
Accessibility Policy
The Office of Attorney General recognizes the importance of making the web site available to the largest possible audience and has attempted to design the site to be accessible.
Limitation of Liabilities
Under no circumstances, including but not limited to, negligence, shall the Office of Attorney General nor any officer, or employee of the Office of Attorney General be liable for any special and/or consequential damages that may result from the use of or the inability to access or use this WEB SITE, even if the Pennsylvania Office of Attorney General has been advised of the possibility of such damages. Applicable law may not allow the limitation or exclusion of liability or consequential damages, so the above limitation or exclusion may not apply to you. In no event shall the Pennsylvania Office of Attorney General’s total liability to you for all damages, losses, and causes of action (whether in contract, tort, (including but not limited to negligence) or otherwise) exceed the amount paid by you, if any, to access this WEB SITE.
Web Browser Support
This website has been tested and supports the following Internet browser programs:
Mobile devices
Generally speaking, We support the latest versions of each major platform’s default browsers. Note that proxy browsers (such as Opera Mini, Opera Mobile’s Turbo mode, UC Browser Mini, Amazon Silk) are not all supported.
Chrome
Firefox
Safari
Android Browser & WebView
Microsoft Edge
Android
Supported
Supported
Desktop browsers
Similarly, the latest versions of most desktop browsers are supported.
Chrome
Firefox
Internet Explorer
Microsoft Edge
Opera
Safari
Mac
Supported
Not supported
*Note: Our Employment site is only fully-supported in Internet Explorer 11.
Pennsylvania Office of Attorney General Privacy Policy
The Office of Attorney General maintains this site as a public service. The following information outlines the privacy policy regarding this site.
Information Collected
Some information is collected from you automatically when you view the Office of Attorney General’s pages and download information. This may include your Internet Protocol address assigned by your Internet Service Provider, domain name and the type of browser and operating system you used, the date and time you accessed the web site, the pages you requested and visited, and the site you linked from to reach the Office of Attorney General’s site. This information is collected for statistical analysis using third-party or proprietary software programs to create summary statistics. The statistics are used for the purpose of determining what information is of most and least interest to all visitors and identifying system performance or problem areas. This information is not collected for nor will it be used for commercial marketing purposes.
If during your visit, you voluntarily provide personally identifiable information, we will collect such information. Examples of this information may include:
An email address if you are subscribing or unsubscribing to offerings on the site and/or communicating to us via email;
Information you voluntarily submit for other services offered on the site;
Other information volunteered, such as, but not limited to, the content of email.
Please note that the information collected, whether or not personally identifiable, is not limited to text characters and may include audio, video and other graphic formats you send us. Information is retained in accordance with existing laws, rules, regulations and other policies.
Public Disclosure
As a general rule, we do not disclose any personally identifiable information collected online except where you have given us permission, or when the information is public information under applicable laws. Visitors should be aware that information collected on the web site may be subject to examination or inspection, if such information is a public record or not otherwise protected from disclosure.
Cookies
Cookies are simple text files stored by your web browser to provide a method of distinguishing among visitors to web sites that allow customized features such as a ‘shopping cart’ feature for online purchasing. At times, the Office of Attorney General may occasionally use ‘cookies’ to customize your browser experience. The cookies that are created on your computer by using our web site do not contain personally identifiable information, nor are they used to construct individual profiles of visitors, and they do not compromise your privacy or security. You can refuse the cookie or delete the cookie file from your computer at any time by using any one of a number of widely available methods. Before taking such steps, you should be aware that some web sites may not work properly if you choose to block the placement of cookies on your computer. You will need to determine whether enabling cookies outweigh privacy concerns.
Please note that the Pennsylvania Attorney General’s web site has links to other web sites. When you link to one of these sites, you are subject to the privacy policy of that new site and the privacy policy of the Attorney General’s site is no longer applicable. Additionally, the Office of Attorney General cannot control the use of cookies at these new sites.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
The Pennsylvania Office of Attorney General may amend this policy from time to time. We will prominently display on this website any substantial change in the way we use your personal information.
Pennsylvania Office of Attorney General Terms of Use and Linking Policy
The Pennsylvania Office of Attorney General’s web site is owned and operated by the Pennsylvania Office of Attorney General and provided as a public service to the citizens of Pennsylvania and visitors throughout the world. The contents of this web site are published for information purposes only and are subject to change without notice.
All copyrighted material must be kept intact and unmodified. Modifications of the materials or use of the materials for purposes not granted by the Pennsylvania Office of Attorney General is a violation of Pennsylvania’s copyright laws.
Links to Other Sites
The Pennsylvania Office of Attorney General’s web site provides links to other organizations. These links are provided for informational purposes only and as a service to our visitors. In providing these links, the Pennsylvania Attorney General does not endorse the content, products, services or viewpoints expressed by these external sites. It is the responsibility of the visitor to evaluate the content and usefulness of information obtained from these external sites. Once a visitor leaves the Pennsylvania Attorney General’s web site and links to an external site, our web site Internet policies are no longer applicable and the visitor will be subject to the new site’s policies. Any problems, concerns or issues with these external sites should be directed to the site administrator or webmaster of those sites.
Linking to AttorneyGeneral.Gov
Linking to AttorneyGeneral.gov is permitted under limited conditions. If you link to this site, you may not portray any person or subject in a false or misleading light. You must also refrain from creating frames, or creating other visual altering tools, around the AttorneyGeneral.gov pages. You may not imply that the Pennsylvania Attorney General is endorsing your product or services.
Pennsylvania Office of Attorney General Security Policy
The Pennsylvania Office of Attorney General, as developer and manager of the AttorneyGeneral.gov web site has taken a number of steps to safeguard the integrity of its data and prevent unauthorized access to information that is maintained in agency computer systems. These measures are designed and intended to prevent corruption of data, block unknown or unauthorized access to our systems and information, ensure the integrity of information that is transmitted between users of e-government applications and the State, and to provide reasonable protection of private information that is in our possession.
For security purposes and to make sure this service remains available to all users, the Pennsylvania Office of Attorney General uses special software programs for monitoring and auditing network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise to cause damage to this government computer system. The Pennsylvania Office of Attorney General also uses industry-standard software tools to control access to specific applications and services and to protect data that is transmitted electronically between users and the Pennsylvania Office of Attorney General. These programs help us identify someone attempting to tamper with this web site.
WARNING — If security monitoring reveals possible evidence of criminal activity, information pertaining to such activity may be provided to law enforcement officials.
Unauthorized attempts to upload information and/or change information on the AttorneyGeneral.gov web site are strictly prohibited and are subject to prosecution under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986 and Title 18 U.S.C. Sec.1001 and 1030.
The information contained in this policy statement should not be construed in any way as giving business, legal, or other advice, or warranting as fail proof, the security of information provided via the Pennsylvania Office of Attorney General web site.
Return to menu
